https://www.kkwater.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content01932 852 423sales@kkwater.comLinkedinTwitterFacebookHomeAbout UsThe CompanyPrivacy PolicyWater TreatmentWater TreatmentUV Water TreatmentWater IssuesMarketsMarineRecreational WaterFood and BeverageMicroelectronicsLife SciencesAquacultureDomestic Drinking WaterWell Water / BoreholeEnvironmental Containment TreatmentWaste Water TreatmentProductsAquafineOptiVenn SeriesSwift Beverage SeriesChloRid SeriesTrojanUVLogic SeriesSCD H SeriesUVK SeriesMPR SeriesViqua HomeViqua TapViqua Tap PlusViqua Home PlusViqua ProfessionalViqua Professional PlusIntegrated Home SystemsWater SoftenersWater FiltersReverse Osmosis UnitsReplacement PartsServicing & Spare PartsNewsContact UsPrivacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy applies between you, the User of this Website and KK Water Purification Ltd, the owner and provider of this Website. KK Water Purification Ltd takes the privacy of your information very seriously. This privacy policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us or provided by you in relation to your use of the Website. Please read this privacy policy carefully.Definitions and interpretationIn this privacy policy, the following definitions are used:Data: collectively all information that you submit to KK Water Purification Ltd via the Website. This definition incorporates, where applicable, the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998.KK Water Purification Ltd, We or Us: KK Water Purification Ltd, a company incorporated in England and Wales with registered number is 02487583 whose registered office is at Victory House, Victory Park Road, Addlestone, Surrey, KT15 2AX.User or you: any third party that accesses the Website and is not either (i) employed by KK Water Purification Ltd and acting in the course of their employment or (ii) engaged as consultant or otherwise providing services to KK Water Purification Ltd and accessing the Website in connection with the provision of such services; andWebsite: the website that you are currently using, www.kkwater.com, and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.In this privacy policy, unless the context requires a different interpretation:The singular includes the plural and vice versa,References to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices of this privacy policy;A reference to a person includes firm, companies, government entities, trusts and partnerships“including” is understood to mean “including without limitation”Reference to any statutory provision includes any modification or amendment of thisThe headings and sub-headings do not form part of this privacy policyScope of this privacy policy This privacy policy applies only to the actions of KK Water Purification Ltd and Users with respect to this Website. It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Website including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites.Data CollectedWe may collect the following Data, which includes personal Data, from you:NameContact Information such as email addresses and telephone numbers, location; in each case, in accordance with this privacy policyFor purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, KK Water Purification Ltd is the “data controller”.We will retain any Data you submit for 12 months.Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to any third party disclosures specifically set out in this policy, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This includes our affiliates and/ or other companies within our group.All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. For more details on security see the clause below (Security).Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Website. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:Internal record keeping;Transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you; in each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.Third party websites and servicesKK Water Purification Ltd may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with certain processes necessary for the operation of the website. The providers of such services do not have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Website.Links to other websitesThis Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. We have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websites. This privacy policy does not extend to your use of such websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites before using them.Changes of business ownership and controlKK Water Purification Ltd may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of KK Water Purification Ltd. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred be transferred along with that part and the new owner of newly controlling party will, under terms this privacy policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.We may also disclose Data to a prospective purchaser of our business or any part of it.In the above instances, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring your privacy is protected.Controlling the use of your DataWherever you are required to submit Data, you will be given options to restrict our use of that Data. This may include the following:Use of Data for direct marketing purposes; andSharing Data with third parties.Functionality of WebsiteTo use all features and functions available on the Website, you may be required to submit certain Data.Accessing your own DataYou have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by KK Water Purification Ltd (where such data is held) on payment of a small fee, which will not exceed £10.SecurityData security is of great importance to KK Water Purification Ltd and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Website.If password access is required for certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.We endeavour to do our best to protect your personal Data. However, transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure and is done at your own risk. We cannot ensure the security of your Data transmitted to the Website.GeneralYou may not transfer any of your rights under this privacy policy to any other person. We may transfer our rights under this privacy policy where we reasonably believe your rights will not be affected.If any court or competent authority finds that any provision of this privacy policy (or part of any provision) is invalid, illegal or unenforceable, that provision or part-provision will, to the extent required, be deemed to be deleted, and the validity and enforceability of the other provisions of this privacy policy will not be affected.Unless otherwise agreed, no delay, act or omission by a party in exercising any right or remedy will be deemed a waiver of that or any other, right or remedy.This Agreement will be governed by and interpreted according to the law of England and Wales. All disputes arising under the Agreement will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English and Welsh courts.Changes to this policyKK Water Purification Ltd reserves the right to change this privacy policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Website and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the privacy policy on your first use of the Website following alterations.You may contact KK Ballers Ltd by email at sales@kkwater.com. 16 May 2018  Call us todayVictory House, Victory Park Rd, Addlestone, Surrey, KT15 2AX Tel:01932 852 423 Fax: +44 (0)1932 847170 Email: sales@kkwater.comOR SEND US A MESSAGEContact Us Widget
Name *
First Last *
Last Company *
Phone Number *
Email *
Location *
Subject *
Message *
Do you wish to receive future emails from us?
Yes
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Addlestone, Surrey, KT15 2AX Tel: 01932 852 423 Fax: 01932 847170 Email: sales@kkwater.comFind us on:FacebookTwitterLinkedin
Copyright
KK Water Go to Top
